Hi, I'm the Star Goddess and here's how to figure out what your Moon sign is.
The Moon in astrology rules your emotions and feelings.
It's a very important planet and because it moves one degree every two hours it changes signs every two and a half days.
The only way to calculate your moon sign is with an Ephemeris, the table of planetary motion.
It is done by the Jet Propulsion Lab and it chronicles the minute movements of each one of the twelve planets, each one of the ten planets and through each one of the twelve signs.
The way you figure it out, is you pick a date.
Mat our producer is born on February first, nineteen eighty five.
So we turn to nineteen eighty five, we look at the month of February.
The left hand side are the days of the week, across the top are the ten different planets.
The first one is the sun, the second two are the moon.
So we look down and we see that his sun is in Aquarius and his moon sign is Gemini which makes him mutable, sparkling, witty and bright.
The critical thing about finding a moon sign is remembering that sometimes the moon changes signs during the day because it moves so quickly.
If you need to figure out what that is, you come down to the bottom of the Ephemeris on the second part of the page and you'll see that it gives the exact moment in time the moon changes from one sign of the Zodiac to the other.
So now you know what your moon sign is.
You can get a better understanding of what your wants and needs are and what you need to do to get those needs met.
So that's better living through Astrology.
I'm Janet Sciales the Star Goddess.